We'll lose.
我们会输的
Then we'll do that together, too.
输我们也要一起输
He did it.
他做到了
And I'm the man who killed the Avengers.
我就是那个害死了复仇者联盟的人
Saw them all dead, Nick, felt it, the whole world, too.
我看见他们都死了 Nick   我感受到了   整个世界都毁了
Wasn't a nightmare, it was my legacy.
那不是场噩梦   那是我造成的
I was shown the end of the path I started us on.
我带领大家走的这条的路的结局 展现在我眼前
I'm not ready.
你还没准备好
No one ever is.
没有人是准备好的
We don't get to choose our time.
我们无法选择
Stop.
停下
I can still save you!
我还可以救你
We are all dead.
我们都死了
-Can you not see it? -Hear me and rejoice.
-你看不到吗  -听我说 你们该感到欣喜
Loki, I thought the world of you. I thought we're gonna fight side by side forever.
Loki   你对我很重要   我总想着我们可以并肩作战直到永远